Finding Aid for Varsinais-Suomi Region immigrant letters, 1880-1966
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Pohjois-Pohjanmaa (Northern Ostrobothnia) Province, letters to
  - Lumijoki
    - Martta Tornberg
      - From: Fiinu Maki. Ont., 1950-1966; 9 items (Reel 16)
  - Oulu praish
    - Otto Vähäkyrö
      - From: Otto Kyro. Minn., 1926; 3 items (Reel 16)
      - From: Anna Hovi. N.Y., 1950-1955; 8 items (Reel 16)
      - From: Maija Sampson. Ont., 1949-1965; 23 items (Reel 16)
      - From: Eila Bomber. Ont., 1955-1965; 10 items (Reel 16)
      - From: Sirkka Kurikka. Ont., 1962-1965; 3 items (Reel 16)